taylormadewebpresence.com 2015-11-28

# TaylorMade Web Presence Privacy Policy | TaylorMade Web Presence

### Main menu

The [TaylorMade Web Presence](http://taylormadewebpresence.com/ "TaylorMade Web Presence - Taylor Bare CEO and Chief Developer") Privacy Policy

[TaylorMade Web Presence](http://taylormadewebpresence.com/ "TaylorMade Web Presence - Taylor Bare CEO and Chief Developer") values your interest, willingness and trust in our services.  We vow to serve you at the best of our ability, and this includes our commitment to safeguard your privacy and security while doing business with us.

Collecting information makes it possible for [TaylorMade Web Presence](http://taylormadewebpresence.com/ "TaylorMade Web Presence - Taylor Bare CEO and Chief Developer") to deliver the kind of service you expect. At [TaylorMadeWebPresence.com](http://taylormadewebpresence.com/ "TaylorMade Web Presence - Taylor Bare CEO and Chief Developer"), you will be asked to share your identifiable information for various purposes, including:

**1-     **To request products and services  
 **2-     **To request information  
 **3-     **To sign up for updates  
 **4-     **To provide feedback  on our products and services

Upon voluntary form submission, your IP Address is recorded. Your visit details are traced for statistical purposes. In addition, content that is transmitted through e-mail correspondence is retained in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. 

[TaylorMadeWebPresence.com](http://taylormadewebpresence.com/ "TaylorMade Web Presence - Taylor Bare CEO and Chief Developer") is not directed toward minors. [TaylorMade Web Presence](http://taylormadewebpresence.com/ "TaylorMade Web Presence - Taylor Bare CEO and Chief Developer") does not knowingly attempt to solicit or receive any information from children.

You will never be asked for sensitive information while filling out a form at [TaylorMadeWebPresence.com](http://taylormadewebpresence.com/ "TaylorMade Web Presence - Taylor Bare CEO and Chief Developer").

The information collected is used to:

**1-     **Provide customers products and services requested  
 **2-     **Respond to your inquiries  
 **3-     **Personalize your experience  
 **4-     **Supply information about and promote our services  
 **5-     **Resolve problems actively and proactively

Personal or business information provided via [TaylorMade Web Presence.com](http://taylormadewebpresence.com/ "TaylorMade Web Presence - Taylor Bare CEO and Chief Developer") is transmitted securely, considered strictly confidential, and will NOT be shared, disclosed, or sold to any third party without your express consent to such action.

Please be warned that when you click on a link that takes you to another Web site, any and all information you provide, is subject to the privacy policy of that site. [TaylorMade Web Presence](http://taylormadewebpresence.com/ "TaylorMade Web Presence - Taylor Bare CEO and Chief Developer") does not control and is not responsible for the practices of such sites.

By visiting or using [TaylorMadeWebPresence.com](http://taylormadewebpresence.com/ "TaylorMade Web Presence - Taylor Bare CEO and Chief Developer"), you agree to the provisions of this Privacy Promise.  If you are not in agreement with the provisions of this Privacy Policy, please refrain from using [TaylorMadeWebPresence.com](http://taylormadewebpresence.com/ "TaylorMade Web Presence - Taylor Bare CEO and Chief Developer").

If you require further information or have questions with regard to the[TaylorMade Web Presence](http://taylormadewebpresence.com/ "TaylorMade Web Presence - Taylor Bare CEO and Chief Developer") privacy policy, you may send your inquiry to Taylor Bare:

[TaylorMade Web Presence](http://taylormadewebpresence.com/ "TaylorMade Web Presence - Taylor Bare CEO and Chief Developer") reserves the right to amend this Privacy Promise at any time, for any reason and, without notice. Any amendments will be effective when posted on the appropriate websites. This policy is effective as of November 26, 2013 and supersedes any and all privacy practices posted prior to that date.

This Privacy Policy is governed by the laws of the State of Texas. UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL [TaylorMade Web Presence](http://taylormadewebpresence.com/ "TaylorMade Web Presence - Taylor Bare CEO and Chief Developer") BE LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES THAT RESULT FROM THE USE OF THE INFORMATION OR MATERIALS ON THIS SITE, EVEN IF [TaylorMade Web Presence](http://taylormadewebpresence.com/ "TaylorMade Web Presence - Taylor Bare CEO and Chief Developer") OR AN AUTHORIZED REPRESENTATIVE OF [TaylorMade Web Presence](http://taylormadewebpresence.com/ "TaylorMade Web Presence - Taylor Bare CEO and Chief Developer") HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.

Thank you for visiting and using [TaylorMade Web Presence.com](http://taylormadewebpresence.com/ "TaylorMade Web Presence - Taylor Bare CEO and Chief Developer")!
